{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "1+1",
      "typeQuestion": 1,
      "response": "2",
      "quizzId": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "1+2",
      "typeQuestion": 1,
      "response": "3",
      "quizzId": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "1+3",
      "typeQuestion": 1,
      "response": "4",
      "quizzId": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "1+4",
      "typeQuestion": 1,
      "response": "5"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "1+5",
      "typeQuestion": 1,
      "response": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "1+6",
      "typeQuestion": 1,
      "response": "7"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "1+1",
      "typeQuestion": 2,
      "response": "1",
      "choix": {
        "1": "2",
        "2": "15",
        "3": "16",
        "4": "Une belle réponse"
      },
      "quizzId": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "1+2",
      "typeQuestion": 2,
      "response": "2",
      "choix": {
        "1": "2",
        "2": "3",
        "3": "16",
        "4": "Une belle réponse"
      },
      "quizzId": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "1+3",
      "typeQuestion": 2,
      "response": "3",
      "choix": {
        "1": "2",
        "2": "15",
        "3": "4",
        "4": "Une belle réponse"
      },
      "quizzId": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "1+1",
      "typeQuestion": 1,
      "response": "2"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "1+1",
      "typeQuestion": 1,
      "response": "2"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "1+1",
      "typeQuestion": 1,
      "response": "2",
      "quizzId": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "1+1",
      "typeQuestion": 1,
      "response": "2",
      "quizzId": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "1+1",
      "typeQuestion": 1,
      "response": "2",
      "quizzId": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "1+1",
      "typeQuestion": 1,
      "response": "2"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "1+1",
      "typeQuestion": 1,
      "response": "2"
    }
  ]
}